(Sheldon:)...scientists observed a 33-day
fluctuation in men's hormone levels.
(Raj:)Interesting.
(Raj:)That might explain my weepy days
in the middle of the month.
(Raj:)You know what I'm talking about.
(Howard:)Okay, forget giant ants.
(Howard:)How about giant rabbits?
(Raj:)Big or small, I don't like rabbits.
(Raj:)They always look like they're about
to say something, but they never do.
(Sheldon:)Rabbits do have a respiratory system
that would support great size.
(Sheldon:)On a side note,
they are one of the few mammals...
(Sheldon:)...whose scrotum
is in front of the penis.
(Raj:)Maybe that's
what they wanna talk about.
(Howard:)Leonard, where do you stand
on giant rabbits and scrotal position?
(Leonard:)I honestly don't care.
Really? Every time we've talked
about unusual animal genitals...
(Raj:)...you've always had some pretty strong
and controversial opinions.